Guide to Barbara Sloan European Union Document Collection, 1951-2004 EUDC
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- EUROPEAN COMMUNITIES General, I.
  - INSTITUTIONS, SPECIALIZED AGENCIES & SERVICES, 9.
    - CONSULTATIVE COMMITTEES
      - Consultative Committees [435], 1968-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 90)
    - COUNCIL OF MINISTERS General
      - COUNCIL OF MINISTERS General [433], 1965-2003; 1.; 9 folders 51" (Box 85)
      - Committee of Permanent Representatives [433.1], 1959-1995; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 89)
      - Agriculture, Council Special Committee on [433.2], 1965-1995; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 89)
      - Trevi Group Official Meetings (Terrorism) [433.3], 1985-1993; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 89)
      - Common Positions, Council [433.4], 1989-1994; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 89)
      - Representatives of the Governments of the Member States [434], 1959-1987; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 90)
      - Summit Meetings European Council [420 C], 1967-2004; 7.; 2 folders 3" (Box 48)
      - List of Summits & Related Documents [420 C], 1960-1995; 8.; 16 folders 10" (Box 48)
    - COURT OF AUDITORS
      - COURT OF AUDITORS General [437], 1975-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 92)
    - COURT OF JUSTICE
      - COURT OF JUSTICE General [425], 1952-2003; 1.; 2 folders 8" (Box 62)
      - Court of Justice; Cases & Decisions [425.2], 1993-2003; 2.; 2 folders 15" (Box 63)
      - European Free Trade Association (EFTA) Court [425.21], 1994-2003; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 64)
      - Court, Weekly Reports of the [425.3], 1991-2003; 4.; 6 folders 29" (Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67)
    - ECONOMIC & SOCIAL COMMITTTEE
      - Economic & Social Committee [426], 1961-2002; 1.; 3 folders 13" (Box 67)
    - EUROPEAN AGENCY FOR MEDICINAL PRODUCTS
      - European Agency for Medicinal Products [4414.312], 1994-2002; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 340)
    - EUROPEAN AVIATION SAFETY AGENCY
      - European Aviation Safety Agency [388.93], 2003; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 39)
    - EUROPEAN CENTRE FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF VOCATIONAL TRAINING
      - European Centre for the Development of Vocational Training (CEDEFOP) [445.12], 1974-2001; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 212)
    - EUROPEAN ENVIRONMENT AGENCY
      - European Environment Agency [628.01], 1984-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 395)
    - EUROPEAN COMMUNITIY HUMANITARIAN OFFICE (ECHO)
      - European Community Humanitarian Office (ECHO) [428.5], 1993-2004; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 69)
    - EUROPEAN FOUNDATION FOR IMPROVEMENT OF LIVING & WORKING CONDITIONS
      - European Foundation for Improvement of Living & Working Conditions (EUROFOUND) [445.6], 1973-2001; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 223)
    - EUROPEAN INVESTMENT BANK
      - European Investment Bank [436], 1962-1997; 1.; 5 folders 20" (Box 90)
      - European Investment Fund [436.1], 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 91)
    - EUROPEAN MONITORING CENTRE FOR DRUGS
      - European Monitoring Centre for Drugs [445.812], 1994-2001; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 227)
    - EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT
      - European Parliament - General [423], 1961-2003; 1.; 1 folder 5" (Box 59)
      - European Parliament, Activities [423.01], 1963-2003; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 59)
      - European Parliament, Organization Rules of Procedure Powers [423.02], 1960-2003; 3.; 4 folders 4" (Box 59)
      - Elections 1979, European Parliament [423.021], 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 60)
      - Elections 1984, European Parliament [423.022], 5.; 1 folder 3" (Box 60)
      - Elections 1989, European Parliament [423.023], 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 61)
      - Elections 1994, European Parliament [423.024], 7.; 1 folder 3" (Box 61)
      - Elections 1999, European Parliament [423.025], 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 61)
      - Elections 2004, European Parliament [423.026], 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 61)
      - Ombudsman [423.03], 1994-2003; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 61)
      - Political Parties, European Parliament [424.9], 1971-2000; 11.; 1 folder 2" (Box 61)
      - Christian Democrats, European Parliament [424.91], 1972-1992; 12.; 1 folder 3" (Box 61)
      - Socialist Group, European Parliament [424.92], 1960-1985; 13.; 2 folder 6" (Box 62)
      - Conservative Group, European Parliament [424.93], 1972-1983; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 62)
      - Communist Group, European Parliament [424.94], 1978-1985; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 62)
      - Liberal and Allies Group, European Parliament [424.95], 1975-1987; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 62)
    - EUROPEAN TRAINING FOUNDATION
      - European Training Foundation [445.13], 1994-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 212)
    - LEGAL SERVICE
      - Legal Service [428.1], 1970-1984; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 69)
    - OFFICE FOR HARMONIZATION OF TRADEMARKS AND DESIGNS
      - Office for Harmonization of Trademarks and Designs [4414.321], 1993-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 342)
    - PRESS & INFORMATION (After 1 July 1968 )
      - PRESS & INFORMATION (After 1 July 1968 ) [4410], 1968-2003; 1.; 2 folders 10" (Box 296)
      - Documentation Questions, General [4410.2], 1974 & 1984; 2.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 297)
      - Press & Information Service (Before 1 July 1968) [428.3], 1960-1968; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 69)
    - PUBLICATIONS OFFICE
      - PUBLICATIONS OFFICE [427], 1970-2000; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 68)
      - European Bookshop Ltd [4410.1], 1969; 2.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 297)
      - Official Journal [427.1], 1958-2004; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 68)
      - Publications & Distributions Policy CCP and SAGAP [427.2], 1973-2003; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 69)
      - CELEX & ECDOC [432.2], 1974-1994; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 85)
    - SOCIAL PARTNERS OFFICE
      - Social Partners Office [428.4], 1975-1986; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 69)
    - STATISTICAL OFFICE
      - Statistical Office [428.2], 1970-2003; 2.; 1 folder 3" (Box 69)
    - TRANSLATION SERVICES
      - Translation Services [342.725], 1958-2003; 1.; 1 folder 5" (Box 22)
  - TREATIES, 10.
    - GENERAL
      - Constitutional Convention, Rules & Organization [422.341], 2002-2003; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 58)
      - Treaties [422], 1965-2002; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 56)
      - Treaties, Development of [422.1], 1956-1994; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 56)
      - Treaties, Interpretation of [422.2], 1968-1998; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 56)
      - Treaties, Revision of (See Also 429.2) [422.3], 1970-1992; 5.; 1 folder 4" (Box 57)
      - Fusion of the Executives; Fusion of the Communities [429.2], 1960-1982; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 70)
      - Intergovernmental Conference 1990/91 [422.3l], 1990-1994; 7.; 2 folders 7" (Box 57)
      - Intergovernmental Conference 1996 [422.32], 1996-1997; 8.; 2 folders 5" (Box 58)
      - Intergovernmental Conference 2000 [422.33], 2000-2003; 9.; 1 folder 2" (Box 58)
      - Intergovernmental Conference 2004 [422.34], 2000-2004; 10.; 1 folder 5" (Box 58)
    - FILES ON SPECIFIC EEC TREATY ARTICLES
      - Article 103 - Economic Policy & Coordination [431], 1963-1993; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 72)
      - Articles 104-109 - Balance of Payments and Cross-border Payments [431], 1968-1998; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 72)
      - Article 115 - Blocking the Import of Goods not yet Regulated by a Common Trade Policy [431], 1964-1984; 3.; 2 folders 11" (Box 72)
      - Articles 169-171 - Infringement Procedure Against a Member State not Complying with EEC Rules [431], 1965-1997; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 73)
      - Article 223 - Trade in Arms, Munitions and War Material [431], 1975-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 73)
      - Article 226 - Derogations Due to Security Concerns [431], 1962-1992; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 73)
      - Article 235 - Right to Take Action Beyond Areas Covered in the Treaty [431], 1958-2001; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 73)
- POLICY AREA, II.
  - AGRICULTURE General, 1.
    - Agriculture General [446], 1958-2003; 1.; 10 folders 56" (Box 229, Box 230, Box 231)
    - Impact of the CAP on Trade [446:382], 1969-2003; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 231)
    - Impact of the CAP on US Trade [446: 382(103)], 1962-2003; 3.; 2 folders 5" (Box 232)
    - Agriculture, Management Committees General [446.1], 1969-2003; 4.; 1 folder 2" (Box 232)
    - Enlargement Third, General Agricultural Regulations [446.12], 1987-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 232)
    - Agriculture Statistics [31: 63], 1965-2003; 6.; 1 folder 5" (Box 5)
    - Agriculture, Applications of Atomic Energy [621.039: 63], 1966-1973; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 390)
    - MARKET ORGANIZATIONS
      - Crop Products, General [446.2], 1999-2001; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 232)
      - Cereals & Derivatives [446.21], 1961-2003; 2.; 4 folders 16" (Box 232, Box 233)
      - Rice [446.211], 1963-2003; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 234)
      - Cereals, Consultative Committee [446.212], 1969-1987; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 234)
      - Sugar [446.22], 1964-2003; 5.; 3 folders 9" (Box 234)
      - Sugar, Consultative Committee for [446.221], 1969-1998; 6.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 234)
      - Fats & Oils [446.23], 1961-2003; 7.; 3 folders 12" (Box 235)
      - Fats & Oils, Consultative Committee for [446.231], 1971-1984; 8.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 236)
      - Textile Plants [446.24], 1967-2003; 9.; 1 folder 2" (Box 236)
      - Flax & Hemp, Consultative Committee for [446.241], 1971-1990; 10.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 236)
      - Fodder [446.25], 1974-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 236)
      - Animal Products [446.3], 1970-1996; 12.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 236)
      - Livestock & Meat [446.31], 1971-2003; 13.; 1 folder 3" (Box 236)
      - Beef & Veal [446.311], 1962-2003; 14.; 3 folders 13" (Box 236)
      - Beef & Veal, Consultative Committee for [446.312], 1969-1987; 15.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 238)
      - Pork, Consultative Committee for [446.32], 1969-1987; 16.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 238)
      - Pork [446.321], 1964-2003; 17.; 1 folder 4" (Box 240)
      - Dairy Products [446.322], 1963-2003; 18.; 5 folders 24" (Box 238, Box 239, Box 240)
      - Dairy Products, Consultative Committee for [446.33], 1969-2001; 19.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 241)
      - Albumin [446.331], 1966-1986; 20.; 1 folder 1" (Box 241)
      - Poultry Products [446.332], 1970-2002; 21.; 1 folder 2" (Box 241)
      - Poultry [446.34], 1964-2003; 22.; 2 folders 5" (Box 241)
      - Poultry & Eggs, Consultative Committee on [446.4], 1969-1996; 23.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 242)
      - Eggs [446.41], 1963-2002; 24.; 1 folder 2" (Box 241)
      - Lamb [446.411], 1975-2003; 25.; 1 folder 4" (Box 241)
      - Agriculture, Specialized Crops Fisheries Forestry [446.412], 1969-1996; 26.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 243)
      - Fruits & Vegetables & Processed Products [446.413], 1962-1999; 27.; 5 folders 19" (Box 242)
      - Fruits & Vegetables Quality Standards [446.414], 1963-2003; 28.; 1 folder 2" (Box 243)
      - Fruits and Vegetables, Consultative Committee for [446.42], 1970-1998; 29.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 243)
      - Potatoes [446.421], 1976-2003; 30.; 1 folder 3" (Box 243)
      - Bananas [446.43], 1993-2002; 31.; 1 folder 4" (Box 244)
      - Wines & Alcohol [446.431], 1962-2003; 32.; 4 folders 20" (Box 244, Box 245, Box 246)
      - Fish & Fish Products [446.45], 1961-2003; 33.; 8 folders 41" (Box 251, Box 246, Box 247, Box 248, Box 249, Box 250)
      - Fish, Consultative Committee for [446.451], 1971-2003; 34.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 252)
      - Forests & Forestry Products [446.46], 1959-2003; 35.; 2 folders 7" (Box 252)
      - Horticultural Products [446.461], 1965-2003; 36.; 2 folders 9" (Box 252)
      - Plants & Horticulture Products, Management Committee on [446.47], 1969-1987; 37.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 252)
      - Tobacco [446.471], 1963-2003; 38.; 2 folders 5" (Box 252)
      - Tobacco, Consultative Committee for [446.48], 1971-1987; 39.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 253)
      - Hops [446.49], 1971-2003; 40.; 1 folder 7" (Box 253)
      - Hops, Consultative Committee for [446.311.1], 1972-1987; 41.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 237)
      - Processed Products [446.312.1], 1962-2001; 42.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 238)
      - Agriculture, Other Commodities [446.331.1], 1963-1998; 43.; 1 folder 2" (Box 241)
      - Agriculture, Prices [446.66], 1962-1998; 44.; 8 folders 31" (Box 273, Box 274, Box 275, Box 276)
    - AGRICULTURE STRUCTURE
      - Agriculture Structure [446.5], 1959-2001; 1.; 4 folders 19" (Box 253, Box 254, Box 255)
      - Coordination of National Structure Policies; Community Agricultural Guidance Program [446.51], 1960-1998; 2.; 1 folder 3" (Box 255)
      - Social Conditions in Agriculture [446.53], 1964-2001; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 255)
      - Consultative Committee for Social Problems of Agricultural Workers [446.531], 1970-1987; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 256)
      - Agriculture, Structural Analyses [446.54], 1964-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 256)
      - Agriculture, Processing & Marketing Improvement Program [446.55], 1975-2000; 6.; 1 folder 4" (Box 256)
      - Agriculture, Integrated Mediterranean Programs [446.56], 1983-1997; 7.; 1 folder 3" (Box 256)
      - Agriculture, Economy & Legislation [446.6], 1963-1998; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 256)
      - Agriculture, Statistics & Analyses [446.61], 1973-2003; 9.; 1 folder 3" (Box 256)
      - Agriculture, Accounting Information Network [446.62], 1963-2003; 10.; 1 folder 5" (Box 257)
      - Agriculture, Medium Term Programs [446.67], 1968-1981; 11.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 277)
    - HARMONIZATION OF LEGISLATION
      - Agriculture, Product Standards, Other Products [446.63], 1971-1987; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 257)
      - Alcoholic Beverages (Behavior) [446.63], 1970-1994; 2.; 1 folder 3" (Box 257)
      - Animal Feed [446.63], 1967-2003; 3.; 3 folders 14" (Box 257, Box 258)
      - Animal Health [446.63], 1982-2004; 4.; 5 folders 24" (Box 259, Box 260, Box 261)
      - Animal Welfare [446.63], 1982-2003; 5.; 1 folder 5" (Box 261)
      - Baby Food [446.63], 1982-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 261)
      - Bread [446.63], 1973-1984; 7.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 261)
      - Candy Industry [446.63], 1971-1976; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 261)
      - Canned Food [446.63], 1964-1989; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 261)
      - Caseins [446.63], 1970-2003; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 261)
      - Cocoa & Chocolate [446.63], 1963-2000; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Coffee and Tea [446.63], 1973-2004; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Coloring Materials [446.63], 1962-2001; 13.; 1 folder 2" (Box 262)
      - Dairy Products Processed [446.63], 1970-2002; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Dietetic Foods [446.63], 1969-2001; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Emulsifiers Thickeners Gelatin [446.63], 1969-1992; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Flavorings [446.63], 1967-2003; 17.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Food Additives General [446.63], 1978-2003; 18.; 1 folder 2" (Box 262)
      - Food Extracts & Similar Products [446.63], 1968-1997; 19.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Food Laws Relating to Codex Alimentarius [446.63], 1971-2001; 20.; 1 folder 1" (Box 262)
      - Food Safety, General [446.63], 1964-2003; 21.; 1 folder 6" (Box 263)
      - Food Supplements [446.63], 2000-2003; 22.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Frozen Foods [446.63], 1983-1992; 23.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Fruit Juices [446.63], 1975-2002; 24.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Honey [446.63], 1974-2002; 25.; 1 folder 5" (Box 263)
      - Ice Cream & Similar Products [446.63], 1970-1976; 26.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Irradiated Foodstuffs [446.63], 1988-2003; 27.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Jams & Marmalades & Jellies & Chestnut Cream [446.63], 1965-2002; 28.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Margarine [446.63], 1968-2002; 29.; 1 folder 1" (Box 263)
      - Materials in Contact with Foodstuffs Contaminates [446.63], 1974-2003; 30.; 1 folder 2" (Box 263)
      - Mayonnaise & Other Similar Products [446.63], 1969-1978; 31.; 1 folder 1" (Box 264)
      - Mineral Waters [446.63], 1970-2003; 32.; 1 folder 1" (Box 264)
      - Non-Alcoholic Beverages [446.63], 1970-1992; 33.; 1 folder 1" (Box 264)
      - Novel Foods [446.63], 1992-2004; 34.; 1 folder 1" (Box 264)
      - Organic Foods [446.63], 1989-2003; 35.; 1 folder 3" (Box 264)
      - Origin, Geographic Designation and Protection of Food Products [446.63], 1992-2003; 36.; 1 folder 1" (Box 264)
      - Pasta [446.63], 1968-1995; 37.; 1 folder 1" (Box 264)
      - Pesticides [446.63], 1965-2003; 38.; 2 folders 9" (Box 264)
      - Phytosanitary - General [446.63], 1997-2004; 39.; 1 folder 2" (Box 265)
      - Phytosanitary Regulations, Dairy Products [446.63], 1971-2003; 40.; 1 folder 4" (Box 266)
      - Phytosanitary Regulations, Meat [446.63], 1962-2004; 41.; 3 folders 14" (Box 267)
      - Phytosanitary Regulations, Fish [446.63], 1988-2003; 42.; 1 folder 6" (Box 267)
      - Plant Pests & Diseases [446.63], 1974-2003; 43.; 1 folder 6" (Box 266)
      - Preservatives [446.63], 1963-1994; 44.; 1 folder 3" (Box 266)
      - Saccharin & Sugar Substitutes [446.63], 1978-2003; 45.; 1 folder 1" (Box 266)
      - Sugars [446.63], 1970-2003; 46.; 1 folder 1" (Box 268)
      - Unit Pricing [446.63], 1977-1998; 47.; 1 folder 1" (Box 268)
      - Wrapping & Packaging [446.63], 1964-2003; 49.; 2 folders 8" (Box 268)
      - Yeast & Other Leavening Agents [446.63], 1973-1979; 50.; 1 folder 1" (Box 269)
      - Permanent Committee for Foodstuffs [446.631], 1965-1999; 51.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 269)
      - Scientific Committee for Food [446.632], 1974-2003; 52.; 1 folder 1" (Box 269)
      - Advisory Committee on Foodstuffs [446.633], 1975-1994; 53.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 269)
      - Office for Veterinary & Plant Health Inspection [446.634], 1994-2002; 54.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 269)
      - Plant Variety Office [446.635], 1994-2002; 55.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 269)
      - Agriculture, Scientific Steering Committee [446.636], 1997-2000; 56.; 1 folder 1" (Box 269)
      - European Food Authority [446.637], 2001-2003; 57.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 269)
    - FINANCING
      - European Agricultural Guidance & Guarantee Fund (EAGGF) [446.63], 1963-2003; 1.; 2 folders 8" (Box 269)
      - European Agricultural Guidance & Guarantee Fund, Guidance (EAGGF) [446.641], 1963-1999; 2.; 3 folders 10" (Box 270, Box 271)
      - European Agricultural Guidance & Guarantee Fund, Guarantees (EAGGF) [446.642], 1962-2003; 3.; 4 folders 18" (Box 270, Box 271)
      - Fraud, European Agricultural Guidance & Guarantee Fund [446.643], 1967-2000; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 272)
      - Levies and Refunds, Pre Fixing and Securities [446.644], 1985-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 273)
    - COMPETITION
      - Competition in Agriculture [446.65], 1963-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 273)
  - BUDGETS & FINANCIAL CONTROL, 2.
    - EUROPEAN COMMUNITIES
      - EC Budget & Financial Matters [432.11], 1974-2003; 1.; 11 folders 52" (Box 76)
      - EC Budget, Special Reports, Parliament [432.112], 1965-1998; 2.; 2 folders 6" (Box 80)
      - EC Budget, Own Resources and Financing [432.113], 1965-2000; 3.; 4 folders 15" (Box 81)
      - Procurement, Contracts Tendered by the EC Commission [432.114], 1984-1998; 4.; 3 folders 9" (Box 82)
      - Fraud, EU Budget [432.115], 1989-2003; 5.; 1 folder 4" (Box 83)
    - EURATOM
      - Euratom Research Budget [432.111], 1968-1998; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 80)
      - Euratom Budget & Financial Questions [462.11], 1961-1993; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 374)
    - ECSC
      - ECSC Budget & Financial Questions [452.11], 1954-2001; 1.; 1 folder 5" (Box 370)
      - ECSC Finances (After 7/1/68) [4418.11], 1968-2003; 2.; 2 folders 6" (Box 363)
    - FINANCIAL CONTROL
      - FINANCIAL CONTROL [4420], 1963-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 366)
      - Financial Control EEC [4420.1], 1970-2002; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 366)
      - Financial Control ECSC [4420.2], 1968-2002; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 366)
      - Financial Control Euratom [4420.3], 1972 & 1973; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 366)
      - Court of Auditors [437], 1975-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 92)
  - COMPETITION, 3.
    - COMPETITION General
      - COMPETITION General [444], 1959-1998; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 195)
      - Competition Policy [444.01], 1961-2003; 2.; 2 folders 3" (Box 195)
    - ANTITRUST
      - Antitrust press materials [444.1], 1960-2004; 1.; 7 folders 23" (Box 196, Box 197, Box 198)
      - Antitrust Decisions in Sectors Except Energy & Steel [444.11], 1960-2003; 2.; 6 folders 28" (Box 198, Box 199, Box 200)
      - Dumping (Antitrust) Intra-Community Trade [444.111], 1960-1986; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 201)
      - Consultative Committee on Ententes [444.112], 1991 & 1996; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 201)
      - Merger Control [444.113], 1990-2003; 5.; 5 folders 24" (Box 202)
      - Antitrust in Energy & Steel Sectors [444.12], 1969-2001; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 203)
      - Energy (Antitrust) [444.121], 1970-2002; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 203)
      - Steel, Antitrust [444.122], 1968-2001; 8.; 1 folder 2" (Box 203)
      - Inspection – Antitrust, General [444.5] (folder missing), 9. (Box 208)
      - Inspection EEC Antitrust (Excluding Energy) [444.51] (Folder Missing), 10. (Box 208)
      - Energy Inspection – Antitrust [444.52] (Folder Missing), 11. (Box 208)
      - Steel Inspection - Antitrust [444.52] (Folder Missing), 12. (Box 208)
    - STATE AID
      - State Aid, Discriminatory Practices Public Enterprise & State Monopolies [444.4], 1968-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 203)
      - State Aid, Decisions [444.42], 1961-2003; 2.; 11 folders 55" (Box 203, Box 204, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Box 208)
      - State Aid, EEA Decisions [444.421], 1965-2003; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 208)
    - MONOPOLIES
      - State Monopolies & Public Enterprise, EU Antitrust Public Enterprise [444.44], 1965-2003; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 208)
  - CREDITS & INVESTMENTS, 4.
    - CREDITS & INVESTMENTS General
      - CREDITS & INVESTMENTS General [4418], 1977-2001; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 363)
    - EUROPEAN COAL AND STEEL COMMUNITY
      - ECSC Finances (After 7/1/68) [4418.11], 1968-2003; 1.; 2 folders 6" (Box 363)
      - ECSC Borrowing Operations [4418.12], 1969-1995; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 363)
      - ECSC Lending Operations [4418.13], 1970-2002; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 363)
      - Investment – ECSC Programs [4418.2], 1968-2003; 4.; 1 folder 2" (Box 364)
      - ECSC, Surveys & Opinions [4418.21], 1974-1986; 5.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 364)
    - EUROPEAN COMMUNITIES
      - Credit, EC Budget [4418.1], 1968-2000; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 363)
      - Borrowing Instruments EC - General NCI (Cohesion and Structural Funds) [4418.3], 1977-2003; 2.; 5 folders 23" (Box 364)
      - Written Questions on Funds [4418.4], 1983-1987; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 365)
  - CULTURAL POLICY, 5.
    - Culture, European Integration [420.5], 1963-1997; 1.; 2 folders 7" (Box 54)
    - Events & Phenomena, European Integration [420.51], 1984-2001; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 55)
    - Cultural Capitals [420.52], 1987-2003; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 55)
    - Broadcasting/Radio/Television [654.1], 1962, 1986; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 406)
    - Printing/Publishing [655], 1980-2002; 5.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 407)
    - Books & Publishing [655.4/5], 1985-2000; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 407)
    - Visual Media [659.13], 1976-1994; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 407)
    - Audiovisual Media [659.148], 1960-2003; 8.; 1 folder 5" (Box 408)
    - Preservation of National & Historical Sites [719(20)], 1968-2003; 9.; 1 folder 2" (Box 408)
    - Cinema & Film Industry [791.4], 1966-2002; 10.; 1 folder 2" (Box 409)
  - CUSTOMS UNION, 6.
    - CUSTOMS - GENERAL
      - Customs - General [443.11], 1977-2003; 1.; 3 folders 9" (Box 180)
    - TARIFFS
      - Tariff Schedules, EEC Common External [443.111], 1964-2002; 1.; 2 folders 10" (Box 180)
      - Tariff Schedules, EEC Common External, List G [443.111.1], 1959-1964; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 181)
      - Customs Classifications [443.111.2], 1986-2002; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 181)
      - Scientific Instruments, Customs procedures [443.111.3], 1985-1999; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 181)
      - Nomenclature & Classifications Tariff (Brussels Tariff Nomenclature) [337.3], 1966-1992; 5.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 12)
    - CUSTOMS LEGISLATION - General
      - Customs Legislation - General [443.112], 1963-2003; 1.; 2 folders 6" (Box 181)
      - Customs Valuation [443.112.1], 1965-2001; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 182)